

DO TUAN HUY

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Mobile: 0985 419 490

YoB: 1996

Address: Ho Chi Minh city

Email: dotuanhuy1302@gmail.com

Portfolio: www.zzz.vn

Linkedin: https://bit.ly/3P5gV1c

Github: https://github.com/thichChiaSe

ABOUT ME

I'm Huy, a front-end developer with over 2 years of experience. My primary focus has been on using React and TypeScript. While my proficiency in .NET and Node.js is at a foundational level, I am eager to further develop these skills and broaden my expertise Being a perpetual learner, I am always excited about exploring new technologies and staying updated on industry trends. My proactive approach to problem-solving and adaptability has been key to my success in diverse work environments.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/SCSS/LESS, JS
- ReactJS, NextJS, Typescript
- Redux Saga
- Nodejs, dotNet (basic)
- Responsive
- Photoshop, Figma
- Styled-component
- Ant design, Devextreme, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material UI
- Git,Postman
- Docker, k8s

EDUCATION

- Central Transport College No.3 (2018-2021)

 Infomation Technology
- CFD training (6/2021-12/2021)
 Major: Front-end Development

SOFT SKILLS

- Work as a team
- · Be optimistic
- Stay focus
- Always learning

WORK EXPERIENCE

FPT INFORMATION SYSTEM (WEBSITE: https://fpt-is.com/)

Position: Developer **03/2022 - 08/2022**

Participating projects: Ihotel (ASP.Net) + Ihrp.v4(React)

- · Participate in research and coding.
- Support everyone on the team.
- Join the knowledge sharing session of the Company.

BAKCO SOLUTIONS (WEBSITE: https://www.bakco.com.vn/)

Position: Front-end developer

09/2022 - present

Participating projects:

- Task management (Reactjs + Typescript)
- Data reconciliation solution (Reactjs + Typescript)
- Datahub (Reactjs + Typescript)
- Ha Tien Gov (Reactjs + Typescript)
- Immuzation record (Reactjs + Typescript)
- Risk assessment (Nexjs)
- TimeKeeping + Asset management (Reactjs + Typescript)

PERSONAL LEARNING PROJECTS

FreshNesecom

12/2021

- Using HTML, SCSS, ReactJS, Flickity,...
- Link: https://react-shop-inky.vercel.app/

Furnitown

7/2021

- Using Standard HTML, SCSS, Javascript, Grunt,...
- Link: https://my-project-02.vercel.app/
- •

Kymco

7/2021

- Using Standard HTML, SCSS, Javascript, Grunt, Flickity,...
- Link: https://project-212ojvdrm-thichchiase.vercel.app/

Wooder Landing Page

6/2021

- Using Standard HTML, SCSS, Javascript, Grunt, Flickity,PhotoSwipe,...
- · Link: Link:https://wooder-topaz.vercel.app